Who wants to go back to Earth?
But don't you want to see the Orion Nebula?
I still think Earth is better.
Yeah, I agree. Can we go home now?
Actually, we can't. Our only spaceship has run out of fuel.
Well, I've got a bag of fuel, so we should be good to go.
I agree with Leafy, let's go!
But the spaceship doesn't run on that fuel.
It runs on contestants.
Bubble, Leafy, and Firey:
What?!
Ha, ha. JK, I meant to say it only runs
on big yellow squishy contestants!
[spongy mumbles]
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Wow, Firey, it's such a relief that
we're returning to Earth!
Yeah!
Hey guys, we'll be landing soon.
Whoa, it looks all different!
Yes, it was renovated while we were gone.
♪ The points are gone ♪
♪ We are free of them now ♪
♪ But we look on ♪
♪ To the moment that we see ♪
♪ The next slice of cake ♪
♪ A step closer to the prize ♪
♪ Brought on by Cake st Stake ♪
The eliminated contestants will
choose who is next to be eliminated.
Bubble and Leafy are immune.
YOYLECAKE!
You know, I've actually got some
yoylecake with me right now.
It's made from the exotic yoyleberry from Yoyleland,
which is on my map, right here!
Om! [bells jingling]
Delicious!
Begin voting.
- Yah!
- Wha?
That's what you get for not calling me beautiful!
Ice Cube, that's one vote.
Gotta put out the fire.
Ahaha...
Woody is next.
Heh...heheheh.
Spongy was already eliminated,
and does not DESERVE TO WIN!
You're not gonna vote me, are you Needley?
No. But call me Needy!
Oh thanks, Needy!
Don't call me Needy!
TD, help me get Firey!
Yeah!
I vote Ice Cube, because she doesn't have dimples!
Firey and Ice Cube are at 3 votes each.
Spongy is at 1, and Rocky has none.
Well, I was going to vote for Firey,
but then I decided to instead, vote for Firey!
Grrr!
Hah!
I choose Ice Cube, because it gets really
hot in the TLC, and I need help cooling it down.
Oh my gosh! Yeah.
Ice Cube would, like, cool things down a ton!
I agree. Ice Cube, the heat is almost unbearable!
Yeah, Ice Cube!
- Ice Cube!
Aw-Iiiiiice Cube!
[Recommended Characters press Icy's button rapidy]
Ice Cube, you have been eliminated.
Ahhh!
That was our Quadruple
Laser Powered Teleportation Device.
Oh no, it's so sad to see Ice Cube gone!
We're not done yet!
Huh, why not?
An eliminated contestant is going to rejoin the game.
Oh yeah, I remember now.
Let's find out who it is at Cake at Stake.
♪ The points are gone ♪
♪ We are free from them now ♪
♪ But we look on ♪
♪ To the moment that we see ♪
♪ The next slice of cake ♪
♪ A step closer to the prize ♪
♪ Brought on by Cake at Stake ♪
Oh my snowflakes, t-that was different!
It was. Do you want to hear
something even more different?
Uh, not really.
[clapping]
Hooray! Woohoo!
Be quiet, Leafy.
Moving on,
856 people voted this time.
They better have voted for me!
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
Stop raging, Flower. Snowball?
Yeah?
You got 8 votes.
Mrtristan626, Englishcreamcakes, Wave3436,
Vader97100, Billymaysx, Thedj95678,
Peg12356, and Dslade6907 voted for you.
They were the only ones.
The oddballs in a group of normal voters.
Is that enough to win?
No, it is not.
Pin and Golf Ball, you only got 13 votes each.
Now my chances of winning went from
1.111 repeating percent to 0.000 repeating percent!
Blocky and Woody only got 24 and 29 votes respectively.
Grrrr!
- Blocky: Hyuh!
- Woody: Ahhhh!
Eraser and Pen. Coincidentally, you both got
exactly 2 to the fifth votes.
Which is?!
32. You are both eliminated.
Ahhhh!
Wait, wait, w-wait! Before you zap me,
I have something to say.
I owe you all five hundred
million vigintillion dollars each,
because I can't afford to pay you all right now.
Surprise, surprise.
Match, you only got 35 votes. Not enough.
OMG! But my blue hair gives me, like,
twenty bazillion bonus votes, right?
No.
Oh no! This is, like, the end!
David only received 41 votes.
Aw, seriously?
So did that clumsy Tennis Ball.
That's it! Now it's time to DE-MAGNETIZE YOU!
Wha? Wah. Oh. Eh. Wh- wah- oh- wh-we-wha-
Ahhhhh!
Now there are only five possible returnees.
Will it be Flower, Needle, Teardrop, Coiny, or Pencil?
Well, I just know I'm going to WIN!
Pencil isn't, because she only got 60 votes.
Well, just my luck!
Coiny, I've had enough of you.
But how many votes did he get?
78.
That's 78 more people that I'm going to have to stretch!
Needy, you only received 103 votes.
Don't call me Needy!
Flower and Teardrop. You are the final two
Flower:
It's... it's, gotta be me, I mean there's
no reason there to be anybody else,
I mean really why would anybody
else vote for anybody but me?
Flower:
I mean I just know it's
gonna be me, 'cause ha-ha, ha, ha!
You know, I hope Teardrop joins.
Let's show the votes.
And Flower rejoins.
Yeah! High-five, Teardrop!
Flower, as a reward, you get a cake.
Finally!
- It's a pizza.
- What?!
So now we have our final six.
That's good.
You each have a fifty-fifty chance
of making it to the finals.
Wow, coolio!
The twenty-first contest is the long jump.
Whoever jumps the furthest wins immunity. Go!
Ru-rumph!
Ble-Hmph!
Hmph!
Hup!
Oh yeah, the Yoyleberries have
some extreme side-effects, sorry.
Hey Flower, you mind going?
Yeah, Flower, go, jump-
I don't wanna jump! Why don't you jump?
I'm next!
Hup!
♪ Blue skidoo, you can too! ♪
Yay! I'm in Yoyleland!
Yah! See? I win!
So, are you all done jumping?
Everyone:
Yeah!
Well, it looks like Leafy jumped the furthest
with a whopping 2,763 miles.
She wins immunity.
Actually I want to give my immunity to Spongy,
'cause I feel bad for burning him.
YAY!
This time the voting is between Flower,
Bubble, Firey, Rocky, and Leafy.
Voters, if you are watching this video, you
should vote who you think should be eliminated.
Vote right now!
You'd better not vote me or I'LL TWIST YOU!
Besides, I'm the least voted for to
be eliminated contestant!
That just shows how WONDERFUL I am!